<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Pacers Bikeshare</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="startLabel">Start</string>
    <string name="PauseLabel">Pause</string>
    <string name="timerVal"> 00:30:00</string>
    <string name="resetLabel">Reset</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_content">Indiana Pacers Bikeshare is a program of Indianapolis Cultural Trail, Inc. (ICT, Inc.) Thanks to the generous gift of the Herb Simon Family Foundation, Indy\'s public bicycle-sharing system is named after our very own Indiana Pacers basketball team.</string>
    <string name="about_content2">Bikeshare is designed to encourage you to use a Pacers Bikeshare bike for all your short trips. Once you\’ve paid your modest 24-Hour Pass or Annual Membership fee, you can take an unlimited number of 30 minute rides for the duration of your Pass or Membership. Enjoy the gold standard of bikeshare programs!</string>
    <string name="how">How It Works</string>
    <string name="how_content">Indy\'s 250 gold bikes are available when you need them near your favorite spots, your office or neighborhood. Once you are done with your ride, simply dock your bike at any of the available stations.</string>
    <string name="checkout_content">
<![CDATA[
        <b>1.</b> Press the kiosk button.<br/>
        <b>2.</b> Follow the instructions on the touchscreen to purchase a 24-Hour Pass.<br/>
        <b>3.</b> When prompted, enter the dock number of the bike you wish to check out.<br/>
        <b>4.</b> The kiosk will unlock the bike from the dock you chose. The dock holding the bike will beep until the bike is removed.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="checkout_content2">
<![CDATA[
        <b>1.</b> Choose one of the locked Pacers Bikeshare bikes.<br/>
        <b>2.</b> Press the silver button on the bike’s dock. <br/>
        <b>3.</b> Touch your Membership card to the square behind the silver button.<br/>
        <b>4.</b> Remove the bike once the locks open (dock will start beeping after the bike is unlocked).
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="checkout_content3">
<![CDATA[
        <b>1.</b> Press the kiosk button.<br/>
        <b>2.</b> Follow the prompts on the touchscreen. When prompted, swipe the same credit card registered with your membership.<br/>
        <b>3.</b> When prompted, enter the dock number of the bike you wish to check out.<br/>
        <b>4.</b> The kiosk will unlock the bike from the dock you chose. The dock holding the bike will beep until the bike is removed.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="ride_content">You now have access to a Pacers Bikeshare bike for unlimited 30-minute trips for the duration of your Pass or Membership.\n\nThe 24-Hour Pass or Annual Membership includes the first 30-minutes of your ride for no additional charge.\n\nAdjust the seat, strap on your helmet and go! Enjoy riding your Pacers Bikeshare bike, and then check it back in at any station with an available dock when you are finished. </string>
    <string name="return_content">
<![CDATA[
        <b>1.</b> Return your bike to any Pacers Bikeshare station by rolling it into an available dock.<br/>
        <b>2.</b> Wait for three rapid blinks of the green light and three quick beeps.<br/>
        <b>3.</b> Once you\'ve returned your Pacers Bikeshare bike at the station, feel free to check out another bike at any time throughout your Pass or Membership period using the same credit card or swipe your Membership card.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="return_content2">
<![CDATA[
        Your Pass or Membership includes <font color=\"red\">unlimited</font> check-outs!<br/>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="map_link">
        <![CDATA[
        <a href=\"http://ftpcontent.worldnow.com/wthr/PDF/bikesharemap.pdf\">Download Station Location Map</a>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="api_content">
        <![CDATA[
        Powered by B-cycle and Pacers Bikeshare<br>To sign up, go to<br><a href=\"http://www.bcycle.com\">www.bcycle.com</a><br>or<br><a href=\"http://www.pacersbikeshare.org\">www.pacersbikeshare.org</a><br>This is a third party ap not affiliated with B-cycle.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="question1">Is it legal to ride a bike without a helmet?</string>
    <string name="answer1">Adults may legally ride a bike without a helmet in most places in the United States, but Indianapolis Cultural Trail, Inc. strongly recommends wearing a helmet whenever riding a Pacers Bikeshare bike.</string>
    <string name="question2">Does Pacers Bikeshare provide helmets for riders?</string>
    <string name="answer2">No. There are hygiene and safety issues with shared helmet use. It is the responsibility of the rider to supply his or her own helmet. Helmets are available for purchase or rental at the following places:\n\nWheel Fun Rentals in White River State Park\n(317) 767-5072\n(317) 730-2290\n\nBicycle Garage Indy Downtown (242 E. Market St., Ste. 101)\n(317) 612-3099</string>
    <string name="question3">Can I check out a bike immediately after returning a bike?</string>
    <string name="answer3">Once a Pacers Bikeshare Bike is returned to a station, you may immediately check out another bike during operating hours and within your membership period.</string>
    <string name="question4">When is the Pacers Bikeshare system available?</string>
    <string name="answer4">The Pacers Bikeshare system is open daily from 5:30 AM until midnight. During closure periods it will not be possible to check out a bike, but bikes can be returned at any time, even when the system is closed. Please remember usage fees are still incurred for any checkout longer than 30-minutes.</string>
    <string name="question5">What if I have a flat tire?</string>
    <string name="answer5">Please return a bike with a flat tire to the nearest Pacers Bikeshare station and report to Customer Service with the 4-digit number on the left side of the frame near the pedals. If it is not possible to get the bike to a station, you must properly secure the bike with the built-in lock and contact Customer Service at (317) 653-1947.</string>
    <string name="question6">What if I am involved in an accident?</string>
    <string name="answer6">If there has been an injury, please call 911 first. Contact Customer Service at (317) 653-1947 at the earliest appropriate time. If you are qualified to administer first aid and there is a need, please help out to the limit of your abilities. If appropriate, contact the police, as well. As in any accident, exchange information with any other affected party and collect contact information from witnesses.</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search by name...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

</resources>
